import { db } from './db'

export async function populate() {
  console.log('Debut de la fonction populate')

  // vérifier si la bd possède deja une liste
  const nbLists = await db.lists.count()
  let listId: number | undefined

  if (nbLists && nbLists > 0) {
    // si la bd possède déjà une liste
    // on récupère la première liste
    listId = (await db.lists.toArray())[0]?.id
  } else {
    // on doit créer une liste
    listId = await db.lists.add({
      title: 'Default',
    })
  }
  const listId2 = await db.lists.add({
    title: 'Test',
  })

  if (listId === undefined || listId2 === undefined) {
    throw new Error("La liste n'a pas pu être créée ou récupérée.")
  }

  // Ajout manuel de données
  await db.cards.bulkAdd([
    {
      question: "Who is the protagonist of the anime 'Naruto'?",
      answer: 'Naruto Uzumaki',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the pirate crew in 'One Piece'?",
      answer: 'Straw Hat Pirates',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Dragon Ball Z', who is Goku's first child?",
      answer: 'Gohan',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the academy in 'My Hero Academia'?",
      answer: 'U.A. High School',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main antagonist in the 'Death Note' series?",
      answer: 'L',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the titan shifter that Eren Yeager possesses in 'Attack on Titan'?",
      answer: 'Attack Titan',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which anime features a shinigami named Ryuk?',
      answer: 'Death Note',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the magical power system called in 'Fairy Tail'?",
      answer: 'Magic',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the captain of the 11th Division in 'Bleach'?",
      answer: 'Kenpachi Zaraki',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Sword Art Online', what is the name of the virtual world where players are trapped?",
      answer: 'Aincrad',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the creator of the 'Fullmetal Alchemist' manga?",
      answer: 'Hiromu Arakawa',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the ultimate technique used by Goku in 'Dragon Ball Z'?",
      answer: 'Kamehameha',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which anime features a girl named Madoka Kaname?',
      answer: 'Puella Magi Madoka Magica',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the cursed finger that Yuji Itadori swallows in 'Jujutsu Kaisen'?",
      answer: "Sukuna's Finger",
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'One Piece', what is Luffy's signature attack?",
      answer: 'Gomu Gomu no Pistol',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is known as the 'Hero of the Hidden Leaf' in 'Naruto'?",
      answer: 'Minato Namikaze',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the notebook that kills anyone whose name is written in it in 'Death Note'?",
      answer: 'Death Note',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which anime features giant humanoid creatures that eat humans?',
      answer: 'Attack on Titan',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the goal of the Homunculi in 'Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood'?",
      answer: "To create the Philosopher's Stone",
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main female character in 'Sword Art Online'?",
      answer: 'Asuna',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which anime features the character Edward Elric?',
      answer: 'Fullmetal Alchemist',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Naruto', what is the name of Naruto's signature jutsu?",
      answer: 'Rasengan',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which anime features the deadly 'Kira' who uses a notebook to kill?",
      answer: 'Death Note',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main protagonist in 'Attack on Titan'?",
      answer: 'Eren Yeager',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'My Hero Academia', what is Izuku Midoriya's hero name?",
      answer: 'Deku',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the full name of the anime 'SAO'?",
      answer: 'Sword Art Online',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which anime features a young ninja who seeks to become the Hokage?',
      answer: 'Naruto',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of the demon fox sealed inside Naruto?',
      answer: 'Kurama',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the captain of the Black Bulls in 'Black Clover'?",
      answer: 'Yami Sukehiro',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which anime features characters using 'Nen' as a power system?",
      answer: 'Hunter x Hunter',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'One Piece', what fruit did Luffy eat?",
      answer: 'Gomu Gomu no Mi',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the strongest of the Seven Deadly Sins?',
      answer: 'Meliodas',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the main goal of Light Yagami in 'Death Note'?",
      answer: 'To create a new world where he is God',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main character in 'Bleach'?",
      answer: 'Ichigo Kurosaki',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which anime features a boy who wants to be the Wizard King?',
      answer: 'Black Clover',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Dragon Ball', what are the mystical orbs that can grant wishes?",
      answer: 'Dragon Balls',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the goal of the 'Akatsuki' group in 'Naruto'?",
      answer: 'To capture all the Tailed Beasts',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which anime features a group of teenagers fighting evil witches in a parallel world?',
      answer: 'Puella Magi Madoka Magica',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the author of 'One Piece'?",
      answer: 'Eiichiro Oda',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the main power used by characters in 'Jujutsu Kaisen'?",
      answer: 'Cursed Energy',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main character in 'Tokyo Ghoul'?",
      answer: 'Ken Kaneki',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Attack on Titan', what is the name of the city where the story begins?",
      answer: 'Shiganshina District',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the goal of Gon Freecss in 'Hunter x Hunter'?",
      answer: 'To find his father',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Which anime features a guild called 'Fairy Tail'?",
      answer: 'Fairy Tail',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the rival of Ash Ketchum in the Pokémon series?',
      answer: 'Gary Oak',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Naruto', who is the leader of the Akatsuki?",
      answer: 'Pain',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which anime features a high school student turned soul reaper?',
      answer: 'Bleach',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the alchemist known as the 'Fullmetal Alchemist'?",
      answer: 'Edward Elric',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the alternate dimension in 'Naruto' where Kaguya can send people?",
      answer: 'Kamui Dimension',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which anime features a hero society where 80% of the population has superpowers?',
      answer: 'My Hero Academia',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who is the main character in 'Demon Slayer: Kimetsu no Yaiba'?",
      answer: 'Tanjiro Kamado',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of Luffy's brother who is also a pirate?",
      answer: 'Portgas D. Ace',
      listId: listId,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the captain of the 1st Division in 'Bleach'?",
      answer: 'Genryūsai Shigekuni Yamamoto',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Dragon Ball Z', who is Vegeta's father?",
      answer: 'King Vegeta',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the school where the students in 'Assassination Classroom' study?",
      answer: 'Kunugigaoka Junior High School',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main character in 'Naruto'?",
      answer: 'Naruto Uzumaki',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which anime features a detective named Conan?',
      answer: 'Detective Conan',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the full name of the character 'Light' in 'Death Note'?",
      answer: 'Light Yagami',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Attack on Titan', what is the name of the Titan that Reiner Braun can transform into?",
      answer: 'Armored Titan',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which anime features a vampire hunter named D?',
      answer: 'Vampire Hunter D',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main antagonist in the 'Naruto Shippuden' series?",
      answer: 'Madara Uchiha',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Dragon Ball', who is the wife of Vegeta?",
      answer: 'Bulma',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the organization that opposes the Survey Corps in 'Attack on Titan'?",
      answer: 'The Marleyan Warriors',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the mentor of Gon in 'Hunter x Hunter'?",
      answer: 'Kite',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which anime features a group of girls who form a school idol group called 'μ's'?",
      answer: 'Love Live!',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Naruto', what is the name of the village where Naruto was born?",
      answer: 'Konohagakure (Hidden Leaf Village)',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the author of 'Naruto'?",
      answer: 'Masashi Kishimoto',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the main female protagonist in 'Sailor Moon'?",
      answer: 'Usagi Tsukino',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which anime features an alchemist named Roy Mustang?',
      answer: 'Fullmetal Alchemist',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the rival of Light Yagami in 'Death Note'?",
      answer: 'L',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Dragon Ball Z', who is Goku's father?",
      answer: 'Bardock',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which anime features characters playing a deadly game called 'SAO'?",
      answer: 'Sword Art Online',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the creature that lives inside Ichigo Kurosaki in 'Bleach'?",
      answer: 'Hollow',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'One Piece', what is the name of Luffy's sword-wielding crewmate?",
      answer: 'Roronoa Zoro',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main character in 'Hunter x Hunter'?",
      answer: 'Gon Freecss',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which anime features a group of assassins known as the 'Phantom Troupe'?",
      answer: 'Hunter x Hunter',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the leader of the Survey Corps in 'Attack on Titan'?",
      answer: 'Erwin Smith',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Naruto', who is the father of Sasuke Uchiha?",
      answer: 'Fugaku Uchiha',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the main antagonist in 'Dragon Ball Z' who turns people into chocolate?",
      answer: 'Majin Buu',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which anime features a high school student who turns into a ghoul?',
      answer: 'Tokyo Ghoul',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main character in 'One Punch Man'?",
      answer: 'Saitama',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the main female character in 'Sword Art Online'?",
      answer: 'Asuna Yuuki',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which anime features a character who can transform into a giant with immense power?',
      answer: 'Attack on Titan',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main character in 'Death Note'?",
      answer: 'Light Yagami',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Naruto', what is the name of the technique used by Kakashi Hatake?",
      answer: 'Chidori',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the goal of Edward and Alphonse Elric in 'Fullmetal Alchemist'?",
      answer: "To find the Philosopher's Stone",
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which anime features the character Shoto Todoroki?',
      answer: 'My Hero Academia',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'One Piece', what is the ultimate treasure that everyone seeks?",
      answer: 'One Piece',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the leader of Team 7 in 'Naruto'?",
      answer: 'Kakashi Hatake',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which anime features a cursed sword named 'Murasame'?",
      answer: 'Akame ga Kill!',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the ultimate power-up form that Goku achieves in 'Dragon Ball Z'?",
      answer: 'Super Saiyan',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Attack on Titan', who is the female Titan?",
      answer: 'Annie Leonhart',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which anime features a young boy training to become the strongest hunter?',
      answer: 'Hunter x Hunter',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the main character in 'One Piece'?",
      answer: 'Monkey D. Luffy',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "In 'Naruto', who is Naruto's mentor?",
      answer: 'Jiraiya',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which anime features a character who can manipulate time using a 'Geass'?",
      answer: 'Code Geass',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the protagonist of 'Black Clover'?",
      answer: 'Asta',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the name of the deadly exam that Gon takes in 'Hunter x Hunter'?",
      answer: 'Hunter Exam',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 'Naruto', what is the name of the technique used by Itachi Uchiha to trap enemies in illusions?",
      answer: 'Tsukuyomi',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which anime features a character with a straw hat?',
      answer: 'One Piece',
      listId: listId2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the main character in 'Fairy Tail'?",
      answer: 'Natsu Dragneel',
      listId: listId2,
    },
  ])

  console.log('Data populated')
}

/*
  let cards: Card[];

  try {
    const response = await fetch('http://localhost:5173/src/models/data.json');
    cards = await response.json();
  } catch (error) {
    console.error('Erreur de Fetch:', error);
    cards = [];
  }

  console.log('Cards JSON:', cards);

  const data = cards.map((e: any) => ({
    question: e.question,
    answer: e.answer,
    listId,
  }));

  await db.cards.bulkAdd(data);
  */

// Fonction pour fetch un JSON
/*
async function fetchJson(url: string) {
  try {
    const response = await fetch(url)
    if (!response.ok) {
      throw new Error(`HTTP error! status: ${response.status}`)
    }
    const data = await response.json()
    console.log('Data JSON:', data)
    return data
  } catch (error) {
    console.error('Erreur lors du fetch:', error)
    throw error
  }
}
*/
